<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.2.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2021-07-14T23:29:23-07:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Janpu, a Machine Learning mentor</title><subtitle>The Talent Circulation Alliance (TCA) is a public-private partnership   that facilitates the stimulation of knowledge exchanges and brain circulation of talent between Taiwan and partners, with the goal of cultivating capable, internationally-integrated, and digitally savvy professionals. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Digital Marketing and You</title><link href="/jekyll/update/2021/07/14/digital-marketing.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Digital Marketing and You" /><published>2021-07-14T03:08:27-07:00</published><updated>2021-07-14T03:08:27-07:00</updated><id>/jekyll/update/2021/07/14/digital%20marketing</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll/update/2021/07/14/digital-marketing.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/dm.png&quot; alt=&quot;Alt Text&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Digital marketing, also called online marketing, is not only the promotion of brands to connect with potential customers using the internet and other forms of digital communication, but also achieve short term convertions to generate money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The goal are (1) find the right influencers and decisions makers of your target company (2) gernerate prospecting with customer lead lists (3) understand user experience and insights of who use the product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you are a member of digital marketing team, you are going to realize quickly not everyone in the company has the same priorities. When we are new comer we incorrectly assume that we must have numerous priorities and multitask to get ahead in business, even though working in this way can deeply affect (and hurt) our productivity. My advice is work on the top priority: make money for the company, not make friend for yourself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When we dig down to the root cause of whatever issue fail a digital marketing team, for example burnout or underperformance, pretty much every time the answer comes up as too many priorities. And the person coming up with new priorities on top of the many plates someone is already spinning? Their boss. It is not uncommon that the developer wants more salary, less work and walking distance to office. But the bosses want the customer to be so happy that they will pay a lot of money for our product, and will tell you the want every features into the product and EVERYTHING IS A PRIORITY.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we can not make everyone happy, just focus on top priority: Increase Sales and/or Revenue. …Increase Profit. The purpose of our digital marketing team in to bridge the gap between the customers and our product. More importly, retain more paid customers.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">What do I think about Data Scientist</title><link href="/jekyll/update/2021/07/13/what-do-I-think.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="What do I think about Data Scientist" /><published>2021-07-13T20:08:27-07:00</published><updated>2021-07-13T20:08:27-07:00</updated><id>/jekyll/update/2021/07/13/what-do-I-think</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll/update/2021/07/13/what-do-I-think.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/T-1.png&quot; alt=&quot;Alt Text&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;T-Shaped People have deep expertise in a specialist field, coupled with a broad skillset, which allows them to work and collaborate outside their area of expertise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You need to build your knowledge as T-shape, horizontally, financial knowledge, hardware knowledge; at least you need to know enough to communicate with the experts in the field, so you can apply your own expertise to it. Vertically that is your expertise, for example, statistical machine learning, nonparametric statistics (e.g. non-parametric Bayesian Hidden Markov Model), …etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Horizontally, you need to pick up one or two the required undergraduate or graduate courses from each disciplines related to the application you want to go to (let’s say, medical images, electronic manufacturing, investment strategy, consumer e-commerce etc.)
Vertically, you need to master the graduate school courses in your field and be able to keep up with a few recent advanced papers in your field (reproduced and extend to new fields or new applications).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;School prepare you well for general knowledge, but in work place to solve specific problems you will need a lot of “know-how”(which most of time is not your specialty) to solve the specific problem your boss assign to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You need to build your competitiveness on certain domain knowledge; machine learning deep learning skills are just tools.&lt;br /&gt;
In general, project management skills and product management skills are always needed in work place. Winning research proposal writing skills is a must for academic career.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome to Caloudi Talent Circulation Alliance (TCA) 2021 Summer Program</title><link href="/opening/remark/2021/07/05/welcome-to-Caloudi.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to Caloudi Talent Circulation Alliance (TCA) 2021 Summer Program" /><published>2021-07-05T09:57:19-07:00</published><updated>2021-07-05T09:57:19-07:00</updated><id>/opening/remark/2021/07/05/welcome-to-Caloudi</id><content type="html" xml:base="/opening/remark/2021/07/05/welcome-to-Caloudi.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/img/janpu.png&quot; alt=&quot;Alt Text&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your excellencies, students, faculty and staff of the International Summer Program, ladies and gentlemen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is my great pleasure to welcome you to Caloudi and to the International Summer Program. The International Summer Program is one of the most precious gems in the Corporation’s crown. In the span of a few hectic weeks you will make an imprint on our company, on our business community, and on our city. We are truly grateful for this. We are grateful, for the simple reason that the most important part of a corporation is its staff. So by coming here you are helping us to build and develop our company - building it into one that is truly international and pluralistic, in regard to knowledge, culture, and views.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to some of he technical skills that you will learn this summer, I hope you can develop both prodcut development and project development skills during this summer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Product development typically refers to all stages involved in bringing a product from concept or idea through market release and beyond. During this summer each of you will be part of a project team of 3-5 people to experience the end-to-end data product development process by develop a minimum viable product (MVP).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, Project development is a linear process that includes completing certain tasks in order to provide a solution for the client’s requirements. In this case, the time and budget are specified and approved before the project development starts. During this summer, all of you not only need to prioritize project requirements and tasks but also need to
estimate time and budget&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Project and product development serve different purposes. We like to see all of you learn both skills at Caloudi by doing actural product development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I do hope you will share my feeling and that you will be inspired by the unique teaching and learning environment at the Caloudi. And I trust that your stay will make you open to the possibility of returning to Caloudi to pursue a career, to do research, or to work here. You should know one thing for sure: you are welcome today, and you are welcome back!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://scrumguides.org/scrum-guide.html&quot;&gt;Scrum Product Development&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Scrum process. Learn more about certified project management at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pmi.org/certifications/project-management-pmp&quot;&gt;Project Management Professional&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Opening" /><category term="Remark" /><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>